[{"answer": "Well, yeah, I just haven't found one as charming as you yet", "docId": "Hackers.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Right, mom. And I'm still a virgin", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Here's your class", "docId": "Hackers.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "No, you're not in my class", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Yeah", "docId": "Hackers.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Pool", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Who are these guys", "docId": "Hackers.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Razor and Blade", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Listen to this bullshit. ", "docId": "Hackers.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Cool", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Now that's cool", "docId": "Hackers.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Yeah, cool", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Cool", "docId": "Hackers.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "You think it's cool", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Yeah, cool", "docId": "Hackers.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": " It's cool", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": " Loser.  I can't believe you were only eleven when you wrote this. It's quite an impressive virus. my friend, I know how you might feel about narking on your friends, but, we're hackers. For us, there's no such thing as family and friends. We're each our own country, with temporary allies and enemies. I'd like to make a treaty with you", "docId": "Hackers.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "I'm the one who understands you. Now, can we be allies", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "And if I win", "docId": "Hackers.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Make it our first date", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Yo, what's up", "docId": "Hackers.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Big deal. A garbage file's got shit in it, my friend, come on", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Oh wow, we are fried", "docId": "Hackers.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "You're both screwed. I help, we can do it in six", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "You said the worm was untreaceable", "docId": "Hackers.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Launch the my friend virus? You can't do that", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Oh good. Cause I have a few things to tell them", "docId": "Hackers.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Mister, I don't care if I face certain death", "qsentId": 28}]